[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause] The
[Vỗ tay]
noble golden chrysanthemum,
hoa cúc vàng quân tử giàu có héo cũng
though withered, does not leave. The noble golden chrysanthemum, though
không rời đi hoa cúc vàng Thanh Cao dẫu
withered, does not fade. The
có héo cũng không phai màu
golden chrysanthemum club, a club in cultivation,
câu lạc bộ cúc vàng câu lạc bộ trong tu
even if there is
dẫu có
no house,
cũng không làm nhà
will overcome. The
cũng sẽ vượt qua
golden chrysanthemum club, a club of joyful practice of
câu lạc bộ cúc vàng câu lạc bộ an vui tu
Buddhist Six Harmonies. The golden chrysanthemum club, a
pháp Phật Lục Hòa câu lạc bộ cúc vàng
club of joyful practice of Buddhist Six Harmonies.
câu lạc bộ an vui tu pháp Phật Lục Hòa
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
One body in harmony with the master, 2 mouths of the Flower of No Conflict,
một thân hòa đồng chủ 2 khẩu Hoa Vô
3 minds in harmony, 4
Tranh 3 ý hòa đồng duyệt 4
flowers of the East, 5 sounds of the East, 6
bông hoa đông cu 5 tiếng Hoa Đông giải 6
places where flowers are too much.
nơi hoa đông quá
Where there is Six Harmonies, there is joy. Where there is autumn, there is peace.
Ở đâu có Lục Hòa ở đó có an vui ở đâu
[Music] The
[âm nhạc]
golden chrysanthemum club, a club of joyful
câu lạc bộ cúc vàng câu lạc bộ an vui tu
practice of Buddhist Six Harmonies. The golden chrysanthemum club, a
pháp Phật Lục Hòa câu lạc bộ cúc vàng
club of joyful practice, together fulfilling our duties. The
câu lạc bộ an vui cùng nhau làm phận sự
golden chrysanthemum club, a club of joyful practice,
câu lạc bộ cúc vàng câu lạc bộ an vui
together cultivating Bodhi
cùng nhau Thu Trinh
mind, protecting the Three Jewels, spreading
Phát Tâm Bồ Đề hộ Trì Tam Bảo truyền tài
Buddhist teachings throughout the world.
Phật pháp rộng khắp thế gian
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
And the noble golden chrysanthemum, the flower of
và cúc vàng quân tử màu hoa của giải
liberation. The golden chrysanthemum club, practicing for
thoát câu lạc bộ cúc vàng tu tập cầu
liberation, helping everyone. The
giải thoát giúp đỡ cho mọi người câu lạc
golden chrysanthemum club, a club of peace.  Joyful practice seeking
bộ cúc vàng câu lạc bộ an vui tu tập cầu
liberation Golden Chrysanthemum Club
giải thoát câu lạc bộ cúc vàng câu lạc
Peaceful Club Golden Chrysanthemum Club Peaceful Club
bộ an vui câu lạc bộ cúc vàng câu lạc bộ
Golden Chrysanthemum Club are Buddhist practitioners
câu lạc bộ cúc vàng là những người phật
at Ba Vang Temple
tử tu tại chùa Ba Vàng
[music]
[âm nhạc]
Supreme Path
vô thượng đạo
always together Thinking towards
luôn cùng nhau Tính tới
to attain
để có
Supreme Path
vô thượng đạo
[music]
[âm nhạc]